https://www.twoscompany.com/privacy-policy-twos/

NEW! Shop Our Retail Site
VISIT OUR FAMILYOF BRANDS
PRIVACY POLICY
TWO’S COMPANY PRIVACY POLICY
Two’s Company, Inc. respects your privacy. We are committed to protecting the privacy between us and you, the end user. This privacy policy explains our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as stated in this policy. Please review this privacy policy periodically, as updates may occur. Use of www.twoscompany.com is subject to the privacy policy at the time of usage.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experienceYour information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.To improve our websiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 30 days.
DO WE USE COOKIES?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
THIRD PARTY LINKS
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. If a child under the age of 13 provides us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may have this information deleted from our records by contacting us through email at customerrelations@twoscompany.com, by calling us at 800-896-7266 or by writing to us at: Two’s Company, Customer Relations, 500 Saw Mill River Road, Elmsford, New York 10980 USA.
CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may change their name, password and e-mail address at anytime by logging into their web account on www.twoscompany.com and going to 'EDIT ACCOUNT'.
ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
TERMS AND CONDITIONS
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.twoscompany.com
YOUR CONSENT
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 1/2013
CONTACTING US
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. www.twoscompany.com500 Saw Mill River RoadElmsford, New York 10980USAemail: customerrelations@twoscompany.com1-800-896-7266
Two's Company | Wholesale
Privacy Policy - Twos
